The goal of this book is to make the case for digital minimalism, including a detailed exploration of what it asks and why it works, and then to teach you how to adopt this philosophy if you decide it’s right for you.
本书的目标是论证数字极简主义的合理性，包括详细探讨它有哪些要求、为什么有效；然后，如果你认定这一理念适合你，再教你如何践行它。
To do so, I divided the book into two parts.
为此，我把本书分成了两部分。
In part one, I describe the philosophical foundations of digital minimalism, starting with an examination of the forces that are making so many people’s digital lives increasingly intolerable, before moving on to a detailed discussion of the digital minimalism philosophy.
在第一部分，我阐述了数字极简主义的理念基础：先考察有哪些力量正让这么多人的数字生活变得越来越难以忍受，然后转入详细讨论数字极简主义理念。
Part one concludes by introducing my suggested method for adopting this philosophy: the digital declutter.
第一部分最后介绍了我推荐用来践行这一理念的方法：数字清理。
This process requires you to step away from optional online activities for thirty days.
这一过程要求你在30天里远离非必需的网络活动。
At the end of the thirty days, you will then add back a small number of carefully chosen online activities that you believe will provide massive benefits to the things you value.
30天结束时，你再把少量精心挑选的网络活动重新加回来——你相信这些活动会给你所看重的事物带来巨大的益处。
In the final chapter of part one, I’ll guide you through carrying out your own digital declutter.
在第一部分的最后一章，我将指导你完成自己的数字清理。
In doing so, I’ll draw on an experiment I ran in 2018 in which over 1,600 people agreed to perform a digital declutter.
在此过程中，我将借鉴自己2018年开展的一项实验：当时有1600多人同意进行数字清理。
You’ll hear these participants’ stories and learn what strategies worked well for them, and what traps they encountered that you should avoid.
你将听到这些参与者的故事，了解哪些策略对他们很有效，以及他们遇到了哪些你应当避开的陷阱。
The second part of this book takes a closer look at some ideas that will help you cultivate a sustainable digital minimalism lifestyle.
本书第二部分会更深入地探讨一些理念，它们将帮助你培养一种可持续的数字极简主义生活方式。
In these chapters, I examine issues such as the importance of solitude and the necessity of cultivating high-quality leisure to replace the time most now spend on mindless device use.
在这几章中，我探讨了一些问题，例如独处的重要性，以及培养高质量休闲活动的必要性——用这些休闲活动来取代如今大多数人花在无意识地使用电子设备上的时间。
Each chapter concludes with a collection of practices, which are designed to help you act on the big ideas of the chapter.
每一章都以一组实践方法收尾，这些方法旨在帮助你把本章的重要理念付诸行动。
You can view these practices as a toolbox meant to aid your efforts to build a minimalist lifestyle that works for your particular circumstances.
你可以把这些实践方法看作一个工具箱，用来帮助你努力打造一种适合自身特定情况的极简主义生活方式。